let questions = [{"numb": 1, "question": "Betrieb", "answer": "Operation,", "options": ["forward", "Leadership, Conduct", "Operation,", "Task"]}, {"numb": 2, "question": "kreis", "answer": "circle", "options": ["Talent", "Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)", "Assumption", "circle"]}, {"numb": 3, "question": "Anzug", "answer": "Suit, Costume", "options": ["Sideways", "Operation,", "Suit, Costume", "Details ,  Kannada : dattamsha"]}, {"numb": 4, "question": "Vorw\u00e4rts", "answer": "forward", "options": ["circle", "Contract", "Suit, Costume", "forward"]}, {"numb": 5, "question": "bedinungen", "answer": "term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu", "options": ["Frequently", "Backward", "Judgement", "term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu"]}, {"numb": 6, "question": "Leitung", "answer": "Leadership, Conduct", "options": ["Leadership, Conduct", "Backward", "Judgement", "Sideways"]}, {"numb": 7, "question": "Angabe", "answer": "Details ,  Kannada : dattamsha", "options": ["Crucial", "Details ,  Kannada : dattamsha", "Operation,", "Task"]}, {"numb": 8, "question": "Gewitter", "answer": "Weather, Kannada: Havaamaana", "options": ["Weather, Kannada: Havaamaana", "Script", "Operation,", "Crucial"]}, {"numb": 9, "question": "Vierecke", "answer": "Rectangular", "options": ["Details ,  Kannada : dattamsha", "Task", "Contract", "Rectangular"]}, {"numb": 10, "question": "Ablauf", "answer": "expired", "options": ["Sideways", "Script", "expired", "process"]}, {"numb": 11, "question": "Ahnung", "answer": "Assumption", "options": ["Container", "term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu", "trip, Clue, Sulivu", "Assumption"]}, {"numb": 12, "question": "Aufgabe", "answer": "Task", "options": ["Assumption", "buildings", "Task", "Details ,  Kannada : dattamsha"]}, {"numb": 13, "question": "knapp", "answer": "almost kannada: durlabha, virala, saakagada", "options": ["buildings", "almost kannada: durlabha, virala, saakagada", "Container", "Leadership, Conduct"]}, {"numb": 14, "question": "Abfall", "answer": "Wastage", "options": ["process", "forward", "Wastage", "Operation,"]}, {"numb": 15, "question": "Geb\u00e4ude", "answer": "buildings", "options": ["Backward", "buildings", "Sideways", "Task"]}, {"numb": 16, "question": "Vertrag", "answer": "Contract", "options": ["Talent", "Backward", "Operation,", "Contract"]}, {"numb": 17, "question": "Verlauf", "answer": "process", "options": ["process", "Crucial", "Operation,", "term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu"]}, {"numb": 18, "question": "Mangel", "answer": "Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)", "options": ["Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)", "Crucial", "Operation,", "forward"]}, {"numb": 19, "question": "Ruckw\u00e4rts", "answer": "Backward", "options": ["Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)", "Assumption", "Backward", "Wastage"]}, {"numb": 20, "question": "Seitew\u00e4rts", "answer": "Sideways", "options": ["Sideways", "buildings", "Task", "Backward"]}, {"numb": 21, "question": "Gabe", "answer": "Talent", "options": ["Talent", "Contract", "forward", "Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)"]}, {"numb": 22, "question": "Hinweise", "answer": "trip, Clue, Sulivu", "options": ["Assumption", "trip, Clue, Sulivu", "Contract", "Frequently"]}, {"numb": 23, "question": "Dreieck", "answer": "Triangle", "options": ["Triangle", "Crucial", "Script", "Task"]}, {"numb": 24, "question": "Wesentlich", "answer": "Crucial", "options": ["Wastage", "Crucial", "Weather, Kannada: Havaamaana", "forward"]}, {"numb": 25, "question": "Schrifft", "answer": "Script", "options": ["Script", "Crucial", "Rectangular", "almost kannada: durlabha, virala, saakagada"]}, {"numb": 26, "question": "Behalter", "answer": "Container", "options": ["Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)", "circle", "Operation,", "Container"]}, {"numb": 27, "question": "H\u00e4ufig", "answer": "Frequently", "options": ["Frequently", "Crucial", "Triangle", "Talent"]}, {"numb": 28, "question": "Urteil", "answer": "Judgement", "options": ["Judgement", "forward", "Triangle", "Contract"]}];